Steven V. Lam

120 Overhill Road | Upper Darby, PA 19082 (610)-772-1744 <u>StevenVL@gmail.com</u>

Junior Web developer

An Entry-level web developer with experience in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript. Foundational knowledge of business, entrepreneurship, and finance. Knowledge of web development, databases, and servers. Worked in both individual projects and teams to develop full stack applications with varying degrees of complexity.

EDUCATION

PENN LPS BOOT CAMP, Philadelphia

Junior full stack developer Expected completion April 17, 2020

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, Dominguez Hills

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Concentration in Finance May 2015

EXPERIENCE

Trident Group - Devon, PA

2016-2020

Disclosure Analyst

- Managed pipeline of disclosures sent to borrowers.
- Ensured disclosure process was compliant with federal regulations.

College of Business Department Scholars - Carson, CA

2014-2015

Student Vice President-Project Coordinator

- Secured funding for various events throughout the semester.
- Coordinated CSUDH's first Entrepreneurial Symposium involving 5 successful entrepreneurs of varying industries and backgrounds.
- Introduced CSUDH's first "Toro Tank" Competition involving 8 student teams and local entrepreneurs as judges.
- Organized "Meet the Companies" event. An informal meet and greet involving 50 companies and over 200 students.

The South Bay Entrepreneurial Center – Torrance, CA

2014 - 2015

Intern -Center Outreach and Promotion

- Organized monthly events to help promote the entrepreneurial center through MeetUp and various other social media outlets.
- Collaborated with a team to publicize the SBEC through monthly newsletters to a base of approximately 1000 subscribers.

Spectrum Group Real Estate – Irvine, CA

2012 - 2014

Associate

- Located potential commercial and residential redevelopment opportunities using LoopNet
- Generated reports and feasibility studies of targeted properties from primary and secondary sources